麦克斯  我们回来啦
Max, we're back.
真扫兴
Aw, that sucks.
这里没跟我希望中那样  在我们不在时
This place didn't burn down while we were gone,
被一把火烧掉
like I had hoped.
今夜才开始  而且我口袋里有罗马蜡烛烟火筒
The night is young, and I have a Roman candle in my pocket.
你们好  欢迎来到威廉斯堡餐厅
Hi, welcome to the Williamsburg diner.
两个人吗
Table for two?
别闹了  厄尔
Don't be silly, Earl.
是我们啊  麦克斯跟卡洛琳
It's us, Max and Caroline.
我叫厄尔  你们抽烟还是不抽烟
And I'm Earl. Smoking or nonsmoking?
你们回来就好啦
Glad to have you back.
麦克斯  卡洛琳
Max and Caroline!
你们公路旅行回来啦
You're back from your road trip.
正正好错过昨天的班呢
And right on time for yesterday's shift.
我们今天也不工作
We're also not working today.
明天也不太有空
Tomorrow's not great either.
幸好你们回来了
Ugh, thank God you're back.
除了阿憨之外  店里好久没有小妞了  而且...
Besides Han, there hasn't been a girl in here in days, and...
她不是我的型
she's not my type.
你的是那种型
What is your type?
甲型  乙型  还是丙型肝炎啊
Hepatitis A, B, or C?
所以你们给我们带了什么礼物
So what did you bring us?
你们得理解我们的遭遇
Uh, you guys don't understand.
我们坐船被从船上踢下来
We got kicked off a riverboat,
坐飞机差点坠机
almost crashed a plane,
行李和钱都全丢了
and lost everything we own.
讲真  我们没死已经是奇迹了
Honestly, it's a miracle we're alive.
所以...  没礼物吗
So...no gifts?
我们去甜品酒吧
Let's get to the dessert bar
看看他们装修得怎么样了
so we can see the work they did.
而且也能避免被误认是这里的客人
Also so people don't think we're customers here.
我也很等不及去看看
I'm excited to see it too,
现在我跟兰迪真的彻底玩完了
and now that Randy and I are really over,
我答应对甜品酒吧付出我5%的心力
I promise to give the dessert bar my full 5%.
凑个6%吧
Make it 6%.
不然我也没别的事做啊
I mean, what else am I gonna do, hmm?
留步
Stop.
奥列格  别挡着门了
Oleg, stop blocking the door.
我们又不是在跟你约会
We're not on a date with you.
我们想去看看甜品酒吧
We want to see the dessert bar.
行啊
Eh, sure,
但在你们去之前
but before you go in there,
想不想看一张超有爱的
do you want to see a cute picture
我跟苏菲还有芭芭拉宝宝全家福
of me, Sophie, and baby Barbara?
好啊
Sure.
你没说是在浴缸里啊
You didn't say it was in the bathtub.
现在你们不爽
Well, now that you're annoyed
希望你们还有一点赞叹...
and hopefully a little impressed...
我能跟你们坦白
I can tell you
我当时不得不炒了你们的承包商
I had to fire your contractor.
什么
What?
我以为我能比他做得更好
I thought I could do a better job.
什么
What?
结果我不行
I couldn't.
我真是信了奥列格的邪
I can't believe Oleg!
他怎么可以让一个陌生人...
How the hell could he let a complete stranger...
做出这么赞的活儿
Do such an amazing job?
等等  我们还是要去杀奥列格的吧
Wait, we're still killing Oleg, though, right?
因为老娘的箭已经在弦上了
'Cause the wheels are already in motion.
天啊  你看那些门
Oh, my God, look at the doors.
那些装饰线板
And the molding?
还有那些壁灯
And the sconces?
我已经不记得高潮是什么感觉
I don't remember what an orgasm is like,
但我觉得我高潮来了
but I think I might be having one.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
芭芭拉宝宝以为你们死了呢
Baby Barbara thought you were dead.
是不是很好笑啊
Isn't that funny?
没有"文斯·沃恩演戏剧"这么可笑  但啥比得过呢
Not "Vince Vaughn doing drama" funny, but what is?
我们不在这段期间  芭芭拉长大许多啊
Wow, Barbara got so big while we were gone.
你得让她休息休息  她遗传到了
You got to give her a break, 'cause she got
她肥索舅舅的基因
her Uncle Fatso's genes.
对了  苏菲  谢谢你在我们不在时
By the way, Sophie, thank you for watching our horse
帮忙照顾我们的马
while we were gone.
他是我最爱的室友了
He's my favorite roommate.
太客气了啦
Aww, well, you know what,
朋友间本该互相照应
that's what friends are for.
我也相信轮到我有需要时
And I'm sure you would do the same for me
你也会帮忙我
if I needed a favor.
-当然会啦  -太好了  因为我需要帮忙
- Of course we would. - Good, 'cause I need a favor.
是这样的
Yeah, see,
我加入了一个了妈妈帮
I joined this mommy support group, you know,
就是比如确保我有正确把宝宝朝上抱
to make sure that I'm holding the baby up right,
又或者是
or you know,
让自己不会在别人
that I don't get too jealous
夸奖她的时候太嫉妒
when people compliment her.
就是正常妈妈该懂的事情
The standard mom stuff.
所以需要帮忙什么呢
So what's the favor?
我最多能帮到B级重罪的忙
I'll do anything up to a Class B felony.
我还有一次才会被三振出局
I still have one strike left.
我要办派对
Well, I'm hosting,
而到时候肯定会有很多乱拉屎撒尿的宝宝
and there are gonna be a lot of sloppy babies there,
所以我想找个垃圾堆做场地
so I'm looking for a real dump.
我能借用你们家吗
Can I use your place?
苏菲  我觉得不太...
Sophie, I don't think--
太谢谢你们了
Thank you, girls.
你们最好了
Yeah, you're the best,
无论芭芭拉怎么跟朋友说你们坏话都不会改变
no matter what baby Barbara tells her friends.
我还以为芭芭拉喜欢我呢
I thought Barbara liked me.
我要发短信跟她谈谈
I'm gonna text her.
你好  我叫鲍比
Oh, hey. I'm Bobby.
你们酒吧是我装修的
I did the work on your bar.
想必你们就是麦克斯与卡洛琳吧
You must be Max and Caroline.
我是麦洛琳  她是卡克斯
I'm Maroline, and this is Cax.
-我是说  -直接说下去吧
-I mean-- -Yeah, let's just move past it.
我们就是你说的人
Uh, we're who you said.
希望你们喜欢
Well, I hope you like it.
我唯一得到的指导  来自你们朋友奥列格
The only guidance I got was from your friend Oleg,
他一直不停地说"再骚浪贱一点"
who just kept saying "Sluttier."
然后他就给我看了一张他在浴缸里的照片
And then he showed me a picture of him in the bathtub.
你装修得超赞
You did an amazing job.
你弄的那些门把[龟头]什么的
I mean, what you did with those knobs.
抛光铜色
Polished brass.
感觉你很想抛光他的"铜头"啊
Looks like you want to polish his brass.
你喜欢壁灯的雾面罩子吗
And how do you like the satin on the sconces?
天啊
Oh, my God.
我膝盖都发软  合不拢腿了
My knees are wiggling.
你喜欢吗
You like that?
-还有这装饰线板的做工  -爱死了
- And the finish on the molding? - Oh, love it!
她爱到都要跟装饰线板"做"了吧
I think she's about to finish on the molding.
你是唯一一个懂我想要什么
You're the only man who knew what I wanted
而且不需要我反复说三遍后
without me having to tell him three times
干脆放弃了的男人
and then give up.
那就好
Hey, great.
我会告诉老板你很喜欢
I'll tell the boss you liked it.
"鲍比  你又成功啦"
"Bobby, you did it again."
怕你没懂我的笑点  我就是老板
In case you missed it, I'm the boss.
你懂了吗  因为他扮老板
See, 'cause he's the boss,
所以他是在对自己说
so he was telling himself.
笑点太深她不懂
It's too many levels for her.
听我说  我也差不多该走了
Hey, um, listen, I should probably get going,
但如果你有任何需要
but if you need anything else,
记得打给我
you can call me.
或打给我老板  任何时候都行
Or my boss. Anytime.
那我可能就两个都打就行了
Well, I might just have to call you both.
炒[再见]
Ciao!
还"炒"呢
"Ciao"?
除非你后面是要接"面"
Unless you're gonna say "mein" after that,
不然我真不知道你是在说什么鬼
I don't know what you're talking about.
他好可爱啊
He's really cute.
你是这么觉得吗
Oh, you think so?
你真是"超冷静完全看不出来"呢  麦洛琳
You were playing it pretty cool, Maroline.
没关系
Oh, don't worry,
这里的东西你全都可以毁
you can ruin everything in here.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我在乎
I do.
我才刚清理过那张沙发
I just scrubbed the couch.
我们还得待在里面多久啊
How much longer do we have to stay in here?
卡洛琳开始聊她三年级时的校外教学了
Caroline's talking about a third grade field trip.
我在多伦多走丢了呢
I got lost in Toronto.
姐妹们  忽略她们
Girls, ignore them.
社会就忽略她们了
Society does.
你们的宝宝呢
Uh, so where are your babies?
在外面停车吗
Out parking the car?
我就不让芭芭拉开车
See, I don't let Barbara drive yet.
我该让她开吗
Should I?
我们聚会时从不带宝宝
We don't bring 'em to the meetings.
他们只会破坏一切
They ruin everything.
一出生就破坏了我们的"小洞洞"
Starting with our vaginas.
对啊
Oh, yeah,
我老公在我们第一次约会就玩坏我的了
my husband ruined mine on my first date.
是  是这样的  我本以为
See--well, see, I thought
妈妈帮聚会是...
that a mother's group, you know, you--
聊聊宝宝的事情
you talk about your babies.
宝宝们巴不得我们聊吧
Wouldn't they love that?
不是的  这是我们用来
No, this is for us to--
交换"药物"  喝个大醉
to trade pills and get trashed
以及幻想跟我们老公玩一把《消失的爱人》
and fantasize about Gone Girl-ing our husbands.
天啊  那我真是满盘皆错
Oh, my God, I'm doing everything wrong.
我又想起我在84年奥运的不堪回忆了
Yeah, just like the '84 Olympics all over again.
婊姐妹们  大家好啊
What's up, sluts?
这里有个婴儿啊
Ugh, there's a baby here?
要不是我大麻抽晕乎了
If I weren't already stoned,
我现在就开车去别处
I'd drive somewhere else.
我的错
My bad.
是这样的
Yeah, see,
我以为是要交流孩子就寝时间的经验
I thought we were gonna compare notes on bedtimes
以及孩子到底要睡多熟
and how asleep a baby has to be
才可以在他们面前做爱
to have sex in front of it.
你也跟你的健身教练上床吗
You have sex with your trainer too?
我该吗
Should I?
看到你们俩给甜品酒吧做的改变
Seeing what you girls did to the dessert bar
激发了我改善餐厅的念头
inspired me to make some improvements around here.
别告诉我你找到
Don't tell me you found a way
把桌面上黏住的菜单抠起来的方法
to unstick the menus from the tables.
一步一步来好吗
Whoa, one step at a time.
但我的确给这里"整容"了许多
I did give this place more of a facelift
比布拉德·皮特为电影《间谍同盟》拉的皮还多
than Brad Pitt in preparation for the movie Allied.
阿憨  这里看起来一点都没变
Yeah, Han, this place looks exactly the same.
我乱写在墙上的自杀遗书都还在呢
My suicide note is still scrawled on the wall.
看起来还是同一间邮局啊
Yeah, it looks like the same old post office to me.
这里他妈不是邮局
It's not a freakin' post office!
麦克斯  我们真的得过去甜品酒吧了
Max, we should really get over to the dessert bar.
鲍比正在过来看我很不满意的
Bobby's on his way to look at those gorgeous sconces
超美壁灯的路上
I am very unhappy with.
为什么你要用甜品酒吧
Why do you have to use the dessert bar
来当你再见他的借口啊
as an excuse to see him?
如果你喜欢他  你何不直接说
If you like him, why don't you just say,
"你好可爱啊  想看我的马吗"
"Hey, you're cute. Want to see my horse?"
因为淑女都会等绅士
Because a lady waits for a gentleman
主动请求看她的马
to ask to see her horse.
我真不知道你都是跟哪些淑女混
I don't know what ladies you're hanging out with.
貌似完全没有
Apparently none.
鲍比到甜品酒吧了
Bobby's at the dessert bar.
让我先换成
Let me just change into something
比较舒适的穿着
a little more comfortable.
你为什么要把这事搞这么复杂
Why are you making this so complicated?
你为什么不直接说"咱们来喝酒
Why don't you just say, "Let's get drinks
喝完打炮比较不尴尬"
to make the sex less awkward?"
或者你也可以这样
Or you could do that.
你好啊  鲍比  我忘了你会来
Oh, hi, Bobby, I forgot you were stopping by.
她以为她要在这里主持《幸运之轮》呢
She thought she was hosting Wheel of Fortune in here.
我愿意跟她买个母音
I'd buy a vowel from her.
场上亮起了两个A
Well, it would be two As.
你想给我看什么来着
oh, uh, what did you want to show me?
貌似是一点侧乳
Apparently a little side boob.
壁灯
This sconce.
我发现如果我用
I noticed that if I put
全身力气推它
all the force of my body against it,
它就会有点移位
it moves a little.
你看
See?
我...
Ugh, I--
可能被我推进正确位置了
I must have jammed it into place
当时我在测试它生殖力
while I was testing its virility.
不对  是稳定力
I mean, stability.
你看  我就说有点松
See? Told you it was loose.
看来我得一直在这里待着
I guess I have stick around as long as it takes
直到它修好为止
until it's fixed.
那就好  因为在你弄好之前
Oh, good, because I wouldn't feel safe
我都不敢太用力拔任何东西
pulling aggressively on anything until you do.
卡洛琳
Caroline!
我们得赶去医院
We got to get to the hospital.
不用  我没事
Oh, no, I'm fine.
鲍比接住我了
Bobby caught me.
不是你有事  梵娜·超白特
Not for you, Vanna Very White.
我接到一通电话说兰迪在曼哈顿出意外了
I just got a call saying Randy was in an accident in Manhattan.
他肯定是为了来见我
He must have been coming to see me.
在我以为一切没戏之时
Just when I thought it was over,
他又用危及生命的紧急事故把我拐回去
he ropes me back in with a life-threatening emergency.
多严重啊
How bad is he?
因为这些壁灯
Because these sconces
明天就没办法再穿这件裙子了
won't be able to wear this dress again tomorrow.
我只知道很严重  他们打给我
All I know is that it's serious, and they called me
是因为我是他手机里的紧急联络人
'cause I'm the emergency contact on his phone.
好吧  我会尽快回来
Okay. I'll be back as fast as I can.
那我会尽慢干活
I'll work as slow as I can.
我不会告诉你老板  因为他就是...
I won't tell your boss... 'cause he's the--
我懂那个哏  快走
I get it. Let's go.
他还活着
Oh, he's still alive.
谢天谢地他脸蛋没受伤
Oh, thank God his face isn't hurt.
还有  一二三四五六
And--one, two, three, four, five, six.
统统都还在
Yep, they're all there.
他为什么总是不穿上衣啊
Why is his shirt always off?
就像某女演员一样总露胸
He's like Kirsten Dunst in a dramatic role.
我不得不脱掉他上衣嘛  因为他...
Well, I had to take his shirt off, because--
你们懂  他腿断了嘛
well, 'cause you know, he broke his leg.
这里是私人病房
This is a private room.
你们俩不能待在这里
You ladies can't be in here.
我是他的紧急联络人  麦克斯
I'm his emergency contact, Max.
剩下的衣服交给我脱吧
I'll take the rest of his clothing off from here.
你能帮我拿根吸管来吗
And can you get me a straw
这样我们能像喝鸡尾酒般共享这吗啡点滴
so we can share this morphine drip mai tai style?
给你们两分钟时间
You girls have two minutes,
切记  这里是医院
and remember, this is a hospital,
所以不许"瞎搞"
so no messing around.
哎呀  差点忘了我的椰子油
Ooh, that's my coconut oil.
椰子油
Coconut oil?
太棒了  他现在可以吃了
Great, now he's edible.
天啊  麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max.
这活脱就是《难忘情事》里的情节啊
This is very An Affair to Remember.
我更像是"炮完就忘"的那种妹子
I'm more of a Quickie to Forget kind of girl.
不  兰迪大老远跑来纽约见你
No, that Randy came all the way to New York to see you
结果惨遭不幸  出了意外
and then got into a tragic accident
而此刻你在这里  守在他的病床边
and now here you are at his bedside.
麦克斯  我不想把话说太早
Max, I don't want to get ahead of myself,
但咱俩可能都要有男朋友啦
but we might both have boyfriends.
来段庆祝四人约会舞吗
Double date dance?
麦克斯
Max?
你怎么会在这里
What are you doing here?
我的上衣呢
Where's my shirt?
卡洛琳什么时候开始主持《幸运之轮》了
When did Caroline start hosting Wheel of Fortune?
我也是这么评价她这身衣服
Ah, that's what I said!
我接到电话说你受伤了
Um, I got the call that you were hurt,
所以我就过来了
so I came right over,
至于你的上衣嘛
and as for your shirt,
我想那群护士应该拿去做一个抱枕老公了
I think the nurses are making a pillow husband out of it.
兰迪  很难过你的腿伤了
Hi, Randy, sorry you broke your leg,
但我有好消息
but great news.
我喜欢上某人了
I like someone.
我想起来了
Oh, that's right.
你还是我的紧急联络人
You're still my emergency contact.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我忘了把它改回我的健身教练了
I never switched it back to my trainer.
怎么回事  是被躲城管的热狗车撞了吗
What happened? Was it a runaway hot dog cart?
因为那是我最可怕的恶梦
Because that is my worst nightmare...
还有就是我的信用卡被百货公司拒刷
besides having my credit card declined at Kohl's.
但我还是挺过来了
But I lived through it.
我去机场的路上被一辆出租车撞了
I got hit by a cab on my way to JFK.
你是说从机场来的路上
You mean you got hit by a cab
被出租车撞了吧
on your way from JFK.
你是来纽约见我的  对吗
You were in New York to see me, right?
跟踪我  求我跟你复合
Track me down, beg me to take you back,
还激动到扯我的头发
pull my hair a little?
不  我的确是要离开
No, I was--I was leaving.
离开  可你还没...
Leaving? But you hadn't--
我知道啦
Do you know what?
这次意外肯定让他得了"来去颠倒症"
The accident must have given him that "To-and-from-lexia."
我觉得乌比·戈德堡就有这病
I think Whoopi Goldberg has it.
时间到  姑娘们  病人需要海棉擦浴了
Time's up, ladies. Patient needs a sponge bath.
他现在浑身都是椰子油
He's got coconut oil all over him.
麦克斯  等等
Hey, Max, wait.
她才刚到  对吧
She just got here. Didn't she?
我就说吧  他得了"来去健忘症"
Told ya. He's got that "Come-and-go-heimers."
乌比出的那本书里面就有写
Whoopi writes all about it in her book.
非常难懂
It's very hard to follow.
麦克斯  这衣服就像
Max, these are like pajamas
已不在乎自己形象的老夫老妻才会穿的睡衣
for couples who don't care anymore.
你说你自己吧
Speak for yourself.
这上面的狗狗可在乎形象啦
These puppies care a lot.
太好了  她们都走了
Oh, good, they're all gone.
她们都把石膏写满了  完全不给我留地儿
They left me zero room to sign his cast.
我想回甜品酒吧
I want to get back to the dessert bar
趁鲍比还没走
while Bobby's still there
没准因为干活还出了点汗
and possibly working up a little sweat.
快去吧  我会帮你打卡
Go ahead. I'll punch you out.
但如果你一直早退
But if you keep leaving early,
医院会让你圣诞节也上班
they're gonna make you work Christmas.
护士  我们需要所有人过来帮忙
Nurse, we need all hands on deck.
有个状况代号41的病人
We've got a 41 in here,
他会乱喷哦
and he's a squirter.
你去吧  妹子  我刚忙完上一个
You--you're up, girl. I had the last one.
"亲爱的兰迪  屁股棒棒哒
"Dear Randy, Nice ass.
护士芭布"
Nurse Barb."
那的确很棒
Well, that is good.
麦克斯
Max.
我没吵醒你吧
I didn't wake you, did I?
不过既然你现在醒了  你为什么来纽约
But now that you're up, why are you in New York?
你说你是在去机场的路上
You said you were on your way to the airport
出意外受伤的
when you got hurt?
是的
I was.
所以你不是来见我的
So you weren't here to see me.
不是  我是试着不去见你
No, I was trying not to see you.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
麦克斯
Max.
是你跟我分手的
You broke up with me.
用电话分手那次吗
That time over the phone?
你还当真了吗  太扯了吧
You took that seriously? That's insane.
我那是暗示"你要哄我"啊
The "This is a cry for attention" was implied.
而我听到的是"我不能满足于此"
What I heard was, "This isn't enough for me,"
既然我们没办法在一起...
and since we can't make it work, it just--it's--
我很难再去面对你
it's too hard for me to see you.
是是是  我在片场听到你怎么说的了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I heard what you said on the movie set.
在德州吗
In Texas?
你怎么能听到我在片场说的话呢
How'd you hear what I said on set?
我跑去当僵尸临演啊
I was a zombie extra.
长大长点脑好吗
Grow up.
果然是你
That was you.
每个人都说我疯了  因为我当时就觉得
Everyone said I was crazy because I thought
我在片场看见你和卡洛琳了
I saw you and Caroline on set.
我的治疗师还给我开了抗抑郁的药
My therapist put me on antidepressants.
你没错  是他们搞错了
Yeah, well, joke's on them,
因为吊在那里的真的是我
'cause it really was me hanging there.
麦克斯  那太疯狂了
Max, that's crazy.
那你看见我时  为什么不跟我说话
Why didn't you say something when you saw me?
因为你说你现在处境很好
Because you said you were in a good place
你想重新开始  诸如此类的屁话
and you want to move on, blah, blah, blah.
我不想再伤害你了
And I don't want to hurt you anymore.
可现在我想打断你另一条腿
But now I want to break your other leg.
麦克斯  你看咱俩
Max, look at us.
我跑去机场结果被车撞
I ran to the airport and got hit by a cab
是为了赶紧离开这里
trying to get out of here
因为我忍不住想去见你
because I was tempted to see you.
而你闯进医院却不是为了偷药
And you broke into a hospital not to steal drugs.
或许这段感情对我们来说有害无益
Maybe this relationship is bad for us.
这喷得太多了吧
There's just so much squirt!
对卡洛琳绝对有害
Definitely for Caroline.
我想你
I miss you.
我也想你
I miss you too.
那我们不要再相互折磨了
Then let's stop being crazy.
你搬来洛城吧
Move to LA.
如果是六年前
You know, six years ago,
我会毫不犹豫答应你
I would've done that in a heartbeat.
我会扔掉我的泡泡糖香烟
I would've thrown my bubblegum cigs
扔掉我超市袋子里装的双节棍
and my nunchucks in a Safeway bag
心甘情愿做你的女人
and been your lady.
但今时不同往日  我不再是过去的我
But it's different now. I'm different.
我有值得在乎的事物
I care about something,
有人需要我依赖我
and I have people who count on me.
我在这里建立了自己的生活
I've built a life here.
真是作死
Damn it.
麦克斯  你知道我不能丢下我在洛城的事务所
Max, you know I can't leave my firm in LA.
所以现在是怎样
So what happens now?
我们唯有吻别了
I think we kiss good-bye.
不行  干柴烈火一吻就着
Hmm, I think that might set us back.
你已经躺在床上
I mean, you're already in a bed,
而且这裤子超容易脱
and these pants come off real easy.
你应该知道这一点啊
I think you know that.
是啊  我刚忘了
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
那抱一个怎么样
How about a hug?
你真的相信自己能抵挡住咪咪的诱惑吗
You really trust yourself against the girls?
远程视频时都抵挡不住
Not even remotely.
那握个手怎么样
How about a handshake?
这完全不会勾起任何性欲
There's nothing less sexual.
好吧  来两发就松手哦
Okay, but two pumps and we're out.
我没有办法不联想到性
I can't not make it sexual.
你闻起来香香的
You smell nice.
我口袋里有很多牛肉干
I've got a lot of jerky in my pocket.
好消息是
Good news is,
我刚救了一个男人的命
I saved a man's life.
坏消息是
Bad news is,
我把一枚戒指落他身体里了
I left a ring inside him.
你的果冻马天尼
Here's your flan-tini
还有一份一瓶量的龙舌兰酒
and a side of a bottle of tequila.
你干嘛哭丧着脸  卡洛琳
Why are you so sad, Caroline?
我是说  她又没有孩子
I mean, she doesn't have kids.
我挺喜欢那个叫鲍比的
Well, I did like this guy Bobby,
可我又不得不陪麦克斯去看兰迪
but then I had to go with Max to see Randy,
然后我被人喷了一身
and I got squirted on,
没有办法及时赶回来见他
and I didn't get back in time to see him
很可能就此错过幸福一生的机会
and possibly missed a chance at a lifetime of happiness.
这个服务员话也太多了吧
Too much talking from the waitress.
女士们
Uh, ladies,
你们跟孩子的爹都离婚了吗
are all of the daddies still in the picture?
因为要是被抓奸  我可爬不动防火梯
'Cause I can't shimmy down a fire escape
没当年那么麻溜了
like I used to.
你真搞笑
That's so funny.
如果我的门卫不"干"了
If my doorman drops out of the rotation,
我会给你打电话
I'll give you a call.
那我先把我的BB机号码给你
Uh, let me give you my beeper number.
没错
Yep!
我跟我的妈妈帮玩得很开心
I'm really having a blast with my mom friends.
你们有止痛药或大锤子吗
Do you have an aspirin, or a sledgehammer?
为什么你会想跟这些女人玩
Why do you want to hang out with these ladies?
她们太毒了
They're mean.
她们刚才有人想绊倒我
One of them tried to trip me.
对  那是我
Yeah, that was me.
我是为了博取她们的好感
Yeah, I--I was trying to impress them.
苏菲  我希望我妈当时能多关心我
Sophie, I wished my mom cared enough about me
帮我夹夹我的小睫毛
to curl my baby eyelashes
就像你帮芭芭拉那样
like you do for Barbara.
或是出手阻止
Or just to intervene
邻居家的恶狗把我叼走
when a neighborhood dog took me away.
苏菲
Sophie,
你的短信没说清
your text wasn't clear.
芭芭拉是该穿豹纹连体衣配牛仔帽
Should Barbara wear the leopard onesie with the jean hat
还是牛仔连体衣配豹纹帽
or the jean onesie with the leopard hat?
对了  她的趾环我全找不到啊
Also, I can't find any of her toe rings.
苏菲  你是在跟我们妈妈帮聚会的时候
Sophie, are you secretly caring for your baby
偷偷关心自己的宝宝吗
while we're having mom's group?
算了  是啦
You know what? Fine.
我爱我的孩子
Fine, I love my kid.
那你干脆娶了她得了
Well, why don't you marry her?
我该吗
Should I?
不可以
No.
不行  因为我是个好妈妈
No, 'cause I'm a good mom,
好妈妈才不会娶自己的孩子
and a good mom doesn't marry her baby!
至少不会在这个国家娶
At least not in this country.
走吧  宝贝
Let's go, baby.
帮梅根遛狗的人给了她点猫的镇静剂
Well, Meghan's dog walker gave her some cat tranquilizers.
不如我们去商场的停车场试试"药劲"
Why don't we go try those in the Target parking lot?
我真是迫不及待相当妈
Ugh, I can't wait to be a mom
这样我就能搞到上好的猫镇静剂
so I can get the good cat tranqs.
你知道她们没付钱  对吧
You know they didn't pay, right?
抱歉闯进来
Hey, uh...sorry to barge in,
但我忍不住想...
but I can't stop thinking about--
她的小翘臀吗
Her boo-tay?
那张桌子超级不稳
Uh, well, that table is really unsteady.
如果我老板知道了
If my boss knew,
我肯定会气死的
I'd be furious.
就是说嘛
I know, right?
我以为只有我这么觉得呢
I thought it was just me,
但我是说  你自己看嘛
but I mean, look at it, I--
-对啊  -没错
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我是说
I mean...
稳如泰山
Rock steady.
完美到不行
Perfect, actually.
他妈的
Damn it.
你想不到其他什么东西需要修理吗
You can't think of anything else that needs to be fixed?
想不到  这真的很烦
No, and it's really annoying.
你们知道还有什么很烦吗
You know what else is annoying?
你们俩还没搞上
You two not jammin'.
你们俩相互喜欢  还有什么问题吗
You like each other. What's the problem?
-你喜欢我吗  -对
- So you like me? - Yeah.
-好  那我应该打给...  -对
- Okay, so I should call-- - Yes.
那好  我差点就打给我家亲戚
Good, 'cause I was this close to calling my cousins
让他们来把这地方砸了
to come in and tear this place apart.
-我会打给你的  -再会  炒面
- I'm gonna call you. - Ciao mein.
-什么  -没事
- What? - Nothing.
瞧瞧你
Wow, look at you.
看来电影《40岁的老处男》续集
I'm gonna have to put the brakes on that
《40岁的老处女》得先暂停了
40-Year-Old-Virgin sequel.
很抱歉我在你不开心时开心
I'm sorry I'm happy when you're not happy.
我开心啊
I am happy...
为你开心
for you.
我知道你说过你不想说这事
I know you said you didn't want to talk about it,
但为什么你不去洛城跟兰迪在一起呢
but why don't you just go to LA to be with Randy?
我不能去洛城
I can't go to LA.
这里有很多东西
I mean, there's too much stuff here
那里没有  比如说
they don't have there, like...
自由女神像
the Statue of Liberty.
你知道她是我马子
You know she's my girl.
你从来都不想去好吗
You never want to go.
而且人家还邀请过咱们  她说
And she invited us when she said,
"带贫穷过来"
"Bring us your poor."
再说了  我在加州去哪里找大麻呀
Plus, where would I find weed in California?
反正理由说都说不完
I mean, the list goes on and on.
我也不会丢下你
I wouldn't leave you either.